Guide to the Posters for pornographic movies,
Posters for pornographic movies
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Posters for pornographic movies, 1962-1986.
7761
72 posters.
Printed Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Posters promoting X-rated movies.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Posters promoting X-rated movies. Includes a number of films directed by Henri Pachard, Harold Lime, and Leon Gucci; and films starring Joanna Storm, Ron Jeremy, Candida Royalle, Annie Sprinkle, and Eric Edwards, among many others. Also, pressbooks with ordering information for certain movie posters.
SUBJECTS
Form and Genre Terms:
Broadsides.; Ephemera.; Posters.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Baby Rosemary, 1976 (Folder 1)
  Starring Sharon Thorpe, Leslie Bovee, Semantha King, Candida Royalle, John Leslie Dupre, and Ken Cotton. Directed by Howard Perking. Produced by Bill Steele.
- Barbara Broadcast, 1977 (Folder 1)
  Starring Anette Haven, C.J. Laing, Constance Money, Suzanne McBaine, and Jamie Gillis. Directed by Henry Paris.
- Blue Jeans, 1982 (Folder 1)
  Starring Brooke Bennet, David Messa, Sharon Mitchell, Jerry Butler, and Sharon Kane. Directed and produced by John Cristopher.
- Blue Magic, 1981 (Folder 1)
  Starring Candida Royalle, Samantha Fox, Veronica Hart, Jack Wrangler, Ron Hudd, Josie Jones, Merle Michaels, and George Payne. Directed by Larry Revene.
- Burlexxx, 1984 (Folder 1)
  Starring Gloria Leonard, Joanna Storm, Carol Cross, Sharon Kane, Annette Heinz, Ron Jeremy, Jerry Butler, Bobby Astyr, R. Bolla, Honey Wilder, and Rene Summers. Directed and produced by Vincent Benedetti.
- Candy Lips, 1976 (Folder 1)
  Starring Susan McBain, Gloria Leonard, Marlene Willoughby, Dominatia, April May, Jeanette Sinclair, and Lois Luv. Directed by Cecil B. Damill
- Caught from Behind 3, 1985 (Folder 1)
  Starring Rosemarie, Eric Edwards, Raysheena, Sue Wadsworth, Ron Jeremy, and Rhonda Shantell. Directed by Hal Freeman.
- Coed Fever (Pressbook), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Starring Annette Haven, Serena, Samantha Fox, Vanessa Del Rio, and Jamie Gillis. Directed by Robert McCullough. Produced by Harold Lime.
- Confessions of a Candystriper, 1984 (Folder 1)
  Starring Angel West, Beverly Bliss, Nick Niter, Jay Sterline, Desiree Lane, and Karen Summer. Directed and produced by Leon Gucci.
- Corruption, 1983 (Folder 1)
  Starring Jamie Gillis, Kelly Nichols, Tiffany Clark, Tanya Lawson, Tish Ambrose, Alexis X, and Vanessa Del Rio. Directed by Roger Watkins.
- Dallas School Girls, 1981 (Folder 1)
  Starring Bobbi Jackson, Misty Middleton, Tiffany Clark, Mercedes Benz, Ashley Moore, and Velveeta. Directed by John Christopher. Produced by Seamon Louche.
- Desire: For Men, 1981 (Folder 2)
  Starring Carol Connors, Long Jeanne Silver, Nicole Black, Erica Boyer, and Jesse Adams. Directed by Carol Connors. Produced by the Mitchell Brothers Film Group.
- The Devil in Miss Jones, Part 2, 1983 (Folder 2)
  Starring Jack Wrangler, Jaqueline Lorians, Joanna Storm, Anna Ventura, and Georgina Spevin. Directed by Henri Pachard. Produced by James George.
- Dirty Looks, 1982 (Folder 2)
  Starring Beth Anne, Bobby Astyar, Leslie Bovee, Roger Caine, Vanessa Del Rio, Samantha Fox, Ron Jeremy, Veri Knotty, C.J. Laing, Merle Michaels, Sharon Mitchell, Kelly Nichols, Annie Sprinkle, Jack Wrangler, Gloria Leonard, and Al Goldstein. Directed by Chuck Vincent.
- A Dirty Western, 1975 (Folder 2)
  Starring Barbara Bourbon, Richard O'Neal, Levi Richards, Gloria Hope, April Grant, and Starlyn Simone. Directed by Joseph F. Robertson.
- Dutch Treat, 1977 (Folder 2)
  Starring Carrah Major-Minor, Lucy Duval, Christy Kluiver, Roger Caine, and Zebedy Colt. Directed and produced by Navred Reef.
- Everything for Everybody (Folder 2)
  Directed by John Armelo.
- Fast Cars, Fast Women, 1981 (Folder 2)
  Starring Kay Parker, Kevin Gibson, Carolyn Jackson, Al Chiurizzi, Lisa Lane, and Ron Jeremy. Directed by Scott McHaley.
- The Female, 1962 (Folder 2)
  Starring Isabel Sarli, Francisco Rabal, and Jardel Filho. Directed by Leopoldo Torre Nilssen.
- Femmes deSade, 1976 (Folder 2)
  Starring Justina Lynn, Samantha Morgan, Sharon Thorpe, and Starr Wood. Directed by Alex deRenzy.
- Fiona on Fire, 1978 (Folder 3)
  Starring Amber Hunt, Gloria Leonard, Jamie Gillis, Marlene Willoughby, and Sam Dean. Directed by Kenneth Schwartz.
- French Finishing School (Pressbook), 1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Starring Brooke West, Desiree Cousteau, Cathy Grenier, Monique Carriere, and Claude Irisson. Directed by Loic Chalmain. Produced by Richard Tantolini.
- Girls of the Night, 1985 (Folder 3)
  Starring Amber Lynn, Harry Reems, Colleen Brennen, Renee Tyfani, R. Bolla, Jay Sterling, and Peter North. Produced by Godfrey Daniels. Directed by Ned Morehead.
- Great Sexpectations, 1984 (Folder 3)
  Starring Kelly Nichols, Honey Wilder, Eric Edwards, and Joanna Storm. Directed by Henri Pachard. Produced by David Stone.
- Half the Action, 1980 (Folder 3)
  Starring Michael Stapp, Becky Bitter, and Ron Jeremy. Directed and produced by B. Ron Eliot.
- Hot Blooded, 1984 (Folder 3)
  Starring Kay Parker, Angel, Karen Summer, Cara Lott, Colleen Brenner, R. Bolla, Herschel Savage, Ron Jeremy, and Harry Reems. Directed and produced by Godfrey Daniels.
- Indecent Pleasures, 1984 (Folder 3)
  Starring Jessie St. James, Bridgette Monet, Danielle, Janey Robins, Erica Boyer, Eric Edwards, Jon Martin, Dave Cannon, Nick Niter, and Dan T. Mann. Directed by Phillip Jem. Produced by Joe Williams.
- Indian Lady, 1981 (Folder 3)
  Starring Debbie Truelove, Andrea Martin, Rick Valenzio, and Sunny Summers. Directed by Ray Dennis Steckler.
- Jack 'n Jill 2, 1984 (Folder 3)
  Starring Samantha Fox, Jack Wrangler, Carol Cross, Jerry Butler, Taija Ray, Brooke Fields, and Gypsy Lee. Directed by Chuck Vincent. Produced by Craig Horrall.
- Kinky Business, 1984 (Folder 3)
  Starring Tom Byron, Jerry Butler, Tanya Lawson, Ginger Lynn, and Laurie Smith. Directed by Eastman Price. Produced by Jerry Ross.
- Ladies Night, 1980 (Folder 3)
  Starring Annette Haven, Lisa DeLeeuw, Nicole Noir, and Chelsea McClane. Directed by Harry Lewis
- The Little Blue Box, 1979 (Folder 3)
  Starring Jennifer Welles, Leslie Bovee, Gloria Leonard, Sharon Mitchell, Ming Toy, John Leslie, and Jamie Gillis. Directed by Arlo Schiffin.
- Little Often Annie, 1984 (Folder 3)
  Starring Desiree Lane, Nick Niter, and China Lee. Directed and produced by Leon Gucci.
- Long Jeanne Silver (Pressbook), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Starring Long Jeanne Silver. Directed by Alex deRenzy.
- Loose Times at Ridley High, 1984 (Folder 3)
  Starring Andrea Adams, Judy Ellis, Bunny Bleu, Paul Thomas, and Eric Edwards. Directed by Hans Kristian. Produced by William Dancer.
- Love Lips, 1976 (Folder 3)
  Starring Sharlin Alexander, Judy Hutchenson, Anne Nevens, Catherine Osborne, and John J. Buchanan. Directed and produced by Dale J. Martin.
- Loves of Lolita, 1984 (Folder 3)
  Starring Angel West, Karen Summer, Jay Serling, and Doug Bennett. Directed and produced by Geon Gucci.
- Lure of the Triangle, 1978 (Folder 3)
  Starring Patricia Rivers, Mike Cone, Scott Daniels, and Victoria Lee. Directed by Phillip Ronald. Produced by Robert Angove.
- Mascara, 1982 (Folder 3)
  Starring Lisa De Leeuw, Lee Carol, Tiffany Clark, Cintrice, Jinger Jaye, Mistress Candice, R. Bolla, George Payne, and Bobby Astyr. Directed by Henri Pachard.
- Marked for Love (Pressbook), 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Starring Michelle Angelo, Capri, and Kitten. Directed by Adam Clay.
- Naughty Notions, 1976 (Folder 3)
  Starring Sharon Thorpe, Al Poe, Patricia Lee, John Leslie, and John Stagliano. Directed and produced by Duncan Starr.
- Neon Nights (Pressbook), 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Starring Lysa Thatcher, Veronica Hart, Kandi Barbour, Arcadia Lake, Jody Maxwell, Linda Vale, Eric Edwards, and Jamie Gillis. Directed and produced by Cecil Howard.
- Oriental Treatment, 1977 (Folder 4)
  Starring Bob Rose and Kyoto Gee. Directed by Harold Lee.
- Pin-Up Playmates, 1972 (Folder 4)
  Starring Janie Meyers, Candy Lace, and Sandy O'Toole. Directed by Erwin C. Dietrich.
- Pleasure Palace, 1979 (Folder 4)
  Starring Serena, Eric Edwards, Richard Bolla, and Jamie Gillis. Directed and produced by Carter Stevens.
- Sandstone, 1975 (Folder 4)
  Directed by Jonathan and Bunny Dana.
- Satisfactions (Pressbook), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Starring Rhonda Jo Petty, Kay Parker, R. Bolla, John Leslie, Eric Edwards, Chrissy Beauchard, Cara Lott, and Carmel. Directed by Robert McCallulm. Produced by Harold Lime and M. Murray.
- Sensations, 1975 (Folder 4)
  Starring Brigitte Maier, Veronique Monet, Tuppy Owens, and Bent Rohweder. Directed by Alberto Ferro.
- The Sensualist (Folder 4)
- The Sensuous City, 1970 (Folder 4)
- Sex Appeal, 1984 (Folder 4)
  Starring Laurie Smith, Lili Marlene, Tara, and Carol Smith.
- Show Girls, 1986 (Folder 4)
  Starring Joanna Storm, Stacey Donovan, Nina Hartley, Misty Reagan, Jessica Wylde, and Eric Edwards. Directed by Robert McCallum. Produced by Tony Montana.
- The Stimulators, 1982 (Folder 4)
  Starring Cheri Champagne, Maria Sentry, Niko, Silver Star, Vendette, Ron Jeremy, and Dave Ruby. Directed by Phil Prince.
- Stray Cats, 1985 (Folder 4)
  Starring Blair Castle, Danielle, Cody Nicole, Rene Summers, and Carol Cross. Directed by Joseph W. Sarno.
- Supergirls Do the Navy, 1984 (Folder 4)
  Starring Raven, Kristara Barrington, Taija Rae, Carol Cross, Susan Nero, and Paul Thomas. Directed by Henri Pachard.
- Swinging Wives, 1973 (Folder 4)
  Starring Gayle Mayberrie, Ron James, and Linda Richards. Directed by Ernest Hoffer. Produced by W.C. Hartwig.
- Teenage Fantasies (Folder 4)
- The "Ten" Girls, 1980 (Folder 4)
  Starring Carol Jennings, Sharon Cannon, Jamie Vixen, April Jones, Vanessa Hart, and Pamela Dickinson.
- Three Way Weekend, 1980 (Folder 4)
  Starring Dan Diego, Jody Lee Olhava, Blake Parrish, Jerry Zanitsch, Richard Blye, and Karen Stride. Directed by Emmett Alston. Produced by Jerome J. Zanitsch. Executive producer Pat Halloran.
- Trashi, 1981 (Folder 4)
  Starring Lisa DeLeeuw, Carol Dada, Serena, Loni Sanders, Dorothy LeMay, and Sharon Mitchel. Directed by Louis Lewis.
- Up in the Air, 1984 (Folder 4)
  Starring China Lee, Beverly Bliss, Joy Merchant, and Nick Niter. Directed and produced by Leon Gucci.
- Velvet High, 1981 (Folder 4)
  Starring Misty Middleton, Carolyn Sand, Merle Michaels, Christie Ford, Jerry Butler, and Greg Lyons. Directed by John Christopher. Produced by Seamon Loche.
- Voluptuous Graduates (Folder 4)
  Starring Sally Marshall, Penny Warden, Rita Foster, and Carol Anne Wood.
- Wet Dreams, 1985 (Folder 4)
  Starring Cody Nicole, Rene Summers, Taija Rae, Kelly Nichols, Sharon Kane, and Carol Cross. Directed by Henri Pachard.
- The Widespread Scandals of Lydia Lace, 1982 (Folder 4)
  Starring Lee Caroll, Ashley Moore, Joana Storm, and Sharon Mitchell. Directed by Henri Pachard. Produced by Vanto Productions, Inc.
- Women at Play, 1984 (Folder 4)
  Starring Paula Meadows, Sharon Kane, Tiger, Daniele, Cara Lott, Sharon Michell, and Billy James. Directed by Ron Dorfman.
- Young Nurses in Love, 1984 (Folder 4)
  Starring Nicole Blanc, Beverly Bliss, Crystal Blue, Joy Merchant, Nick Niter, and Francois. Directed and produced by Leon Gucci.